KRZYSZTOF JANIEC

FULL-STACK DEVELOPER



✓ contact@kjaniec.dev

https://kjaniec.dev

https://github.com/kjaniec-dev

in https://linkedin.com/in/kjaniec-dev

+48 697 924 324

SKILLS

- Typescript
- Java
- Node.JS
- Spring Boot
- React
- Angular
- PostgreSQL
- Elasticsearch
- Redis
- RabbitMQ
- Docker
- Kubernetes

EDUCATION

COMPUTER SCIENCE, 2ND DEGREE

University of Zielona Góra 2012 - 2013

PROFILE

Full-Stack Developer with over 10 years of experience analyzing, designing, and integrating front-end and backend-based applications. Proficient with various platforms, languages. Able to effectively self-manage during independent projects, as well as collaborate as part of a productive team.

EXPERIENCE

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

AMB Software IT Services Sp. z o.o.

2024 - Present

E-commerce - retail

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Biot Sp. z o.o.

2019 - 2024

IoT - lighting management

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Cinkciarz.pl

2015 - 2019

E-commerce - currency exchange

SENIOR EPR DEVELOPER

Trax S.A. / Icomp sp. z o.o.

2012 - 2014

Enterprise resource planning system - Infor Syteline